《黑镜》
(利特曼高中)
∮ 我会名垂千古 ∮
∮ I'm going down in history ∮
∮ 我火力全开 ∮
∮ Hey, yeah whoa-ho, I'm on a roll ∮
∮ 一路高歌  实现梦想 ∮
∮ Riding so high Achieving my goals ∮
∮ 我火力全开 ∮
∮ Hey, yeah whoa-ho, I'm on a roll ∮
(利特曼高中  才艺秀筹款会)
你想试试吗
Hey, you gonna try out?
(高金斯)
- 学校里怎么样  - 还好吧
- So how was school? - Uh, OK, I guess.
刚刚那几个人是你的朋友吗
Those guys back there, friends of yours?
我不知道  他们还没和我说过话
Uh, I don't know, they kind of haven't spoken to me yet.
会好起来的  好吗
It'll get better, OK?
你还是新转来的孩子
You're still the new kid,
你只需要一点时间来适应
you just need a little time to settle in.
大家都会很友好的  这个社区很棒的
Everyone will be so friendly, it's such a good neighborhood.
这个社区的确很棒
It is a good neighborhood.
说得好像你知道似的
Like you would know.
你整天待在你的地下室里
You spend all your time in your dungeon,
研究你的惊天捕鼠器替代品
working on your ground-breaking mousetrap alternative.
∮ 充满野心和活力 ∮
∮ So full of ambition and verve ∮
∮ 我会得到我应得的 ∮
∮ I'm going to get what I deserve ∮
《瑞秋、杰克和小艾希莉》
∮ 亲爱的 ∮
∮ Oh, honey ∮
∮ 我不在乎有谁看到我们震碎地板 ∮
∮ Not concerned who sees us Rippin' up the floor ∮
∮ 亲爱的  你想在哪里跳舞我们就去哪里 ∮
∮ Oh, honey We'll go dancing wherever you choose ∮
∮ 亲爱的  你知道我们不能输 ∮
∮ Oh, honey You know we just can't lose ∮
∮ 我受不了  所以你别装 ∮
∮ Yeah, I can't take it So don't you fake it ∮
∮ 我知道你的爱是我的... ∮
∮ I know your love's my... ∮
(高金斯  自动鼠患控制方法  基于鼠类思考模式  人道  无痛)
(老爸的癖好)
太好了
Yes.
∮ 我充满野心和活力 ∮
∮ I'm stoked on ambition and verve ∮
∮ 我会得到我应得的 ∮
∮ I'm going to get what I deserve ∮
∮ 我充满野心和活力 ∮
∮ So full of ambition and verve ∮
∮ 我会得到我应得的 ∮
∮ I'm going to get what I deserve ∮
看来你们都能跟着唱
I see you singing along.
大家好  我们请到了艾什莉·奥
What's up? We got Ashley O in the house.
- 谢谢你的到来  - 谢谢你请我来  忙忙
- Thanks for being here. - Yeah, thank you for having me, Busy.
你的很多歌都是在梦里得到灵感的  真的吗
A lot of your music comes to you in dreams, is that true?
没错  就是在我睡着时出现在我脑子里的
Yeah, you know, they're kind of in my mind while I'm sleeping
我醒来后必须马上记下来
and so when I wake up I have to really quickly write it down
因为我不想让它溜走
'cause I don't want it to just disappear.
你的歌里宣扬了很多正能量
A lot of positive messages in your music,
充满一种力量
kind of an empowerment vibe.
是的  必须要让人们觉得
Yeah, you know, it's really important for people to feel like
他们能掌控自己的命运
they're in control of their own destiny,
那就是说
and, you know, that means
你要自信自己能成为你想成为的人
having the confidence to be who you want to be.
你的姑妈  她很大程度上是
Now, your aunt, she's kind of the source of
你自信的来源吧
a lot of your confidence, right?
- 她就像是你的导师  - 是的
- Like she's your mentor. - Yeah, you know,
她一直都在照顾我  她也是我的经纪人
she's taken care of me my whole life and she's my manager.
说那个娃娃
Mention the doll.
其实  我来这里是为了
Actually, the reason I'm here is...
向大家介绍  艾什莉替身
to introduce to you, Ashley Too.
艾什莉替身  替身
That's Ashley Too, like T-O-O.
看好了
Watch.
艾什莉  醒来
Ashley, wake up.
- 你好  我是艾什莉替身  - 什么
- Hey there, I'm Ashley Too. - What?
你叫什么
What's your name?
- 大家都叫我忙忙哥  - 很高兴认识你  忙忙
- They call me Busy G. - Pleased to meet you, Busy.
- 我已经开始喜欢她了  - 谢谢
- Wow, I'm into her already. - Thanks.
她其实  她有自己的个性
You know, she's actually, she's got a personality.
- 根据我的个性塑造的  - 类似人工智能吗
- It's modeled right after my own. - Oh, so like an AI?
我们其实还有广告呢
We actually have a commercial,
应该给过你了...
I think we gave it to you and...
广告  没错
The commercial, yeah,
我们应该可以播放了  来吧
I think we're ready to run that now. Fire it up.
开始吧
Let's do it.
你现在可以和你最喜欢的流行歌手做最好的朋友了
Now you can be best friends with your favorite pop star,
- 艾什莉  醒来  - 你好  我是艾什莉替身
- Ashley, wake up. - Hey there, I'm Ashley Too.
根据艾什莉·奥的真实个性
An all-new, intelligent companion
设计的全新智能伙伴
based on Ashley O's actual personality.
- 艾什莉替身能进行有意义的对话  - 天啊
- Ashley Too holds meaningful conversations. - Jesus Christ.
凯蒂  想聊聊男孩子嘛
Hey, Katie, wanna talk about boys?
艾什莉替身能给予化妆建议
Ashley Too gives makeover tips.
我觉得这张可以放在图享上
I was thinking this one for Instagram.
嗯  你挑的图一向不错
Yeah, you always pick a good one.
网上都爱死艾什莉替身了
They love Ashley Too on social.
(我的日记)
∮ 看看你笼中的动物 ∮
∮ See the animal In her cage you've built ∮
∮ 你确定你是在外面吗 ∮
∮ Are you sure what side you're on? ∮
∮ 感受你内心的空洞 ∮
∮ Feel the hollowness Inside of your heart ∮
∮ 一切都在 ∮
∮ Everything right where ∮
∮ 应属的地方 ∮
∮ It belongs ∮
∮ 如果你看着你的倒影 ∮
∮ If you look at your reflection ∮
∮ 那是你所想要的样子吗 ∮
∮ Is it all you want it to be? ∮
∮ 如果你的视线穿透裂缝 ∮
∮ If you could look Right through the cracks ∮
∮ 你会发现自己不敢去看吗 ∮
∮ Would you find yourself afraid to see? ∮
抱歉  不是故意打断的
Sorry, didn't mean to interrupt.
调子很美
It's a nice tune.
歌词有点压抑
The lyrics are kind of a departure.
没什么  就是意识流的风格
It's nothing, it's just a stream of consciousness kind of thing.
艾什莉  你还好吗
Hey, Ashley, everything OK?
嗯  我很好
Yeah, I'm fine.
你按时吃药了吗
You taking your meds?
吃了  你不用担心我
Yeah, you don't have to worry about me.
好吧
Ok.
- 那好  早餐时见  - 回头见
- Alright, see you at breakfast. - See you.
我会让阿玛亚把鸡蛋做成你喜欢的样子
I'll ask Amaya to make those eggs you like.
谢谢
Thank you.
爸爸  我能要一个艾什莉替身吗
Dad, can I get an Ashley Too?
你说什么东西
Sorry, a what?
一个艾什莉替身
An Ashley Too.
- 就是个傻乎乎的艾什莉·奥娃娃  - 不是娃娃
- It's some dorky Ashley O doll. - It's not a doll.
是个想象朋友
An imaginary friend.
当作我的生日礼物  好吗
For my birthday, please.
我考虑一下
I'll think about it.
这周三就是了
It's on Wednesday.
就是什么
What is?
她的生日
Her birthday.
我知道
I knew that.
天啊
Oh, my God.
- 太谢谢你了  - 不客气
- Thank you so much. - You're welcome.
太令人兴奋了
It's so exciting.
艾什莉  醒来
Ashley, wake up.
你好  我是艾什莉替身
Hey there, I'm Ashley Too.
- 你叫什么名字  - 瑞秋
- What's your name? - Uh... Rachel.
- 很高兴认识你  瑞秋  - 我也是
- It's so great to meet you, Rachel. - You, too.
天啊  我是你的铁粉
Oh, my God, I'm such a huge fan.
谢谢  我们互相了解一下吧
Thanks, let's get to know each other.
- 你多大了  - 我今天15岁了
- How old are you? - I'm 15 today.
生日快乐  15岁是个很好的年龄
Happy birthday. Fifteen is a great age.
谢谢你
Thank you.
那么  告诉我  你有兄弟姐妹吗
So, tell me, have you got any brothers or sisters?
只有杰克  她在那边
Just Jack, she's over there.
- 你好  杰克  - 你好  混球
- Hi, Jack. - Hi, fuck face.
杰克  我觉得你的用词不太妥当
Jack, I think you made a bad word choice there.
不用理她  艾什莉
Just ignore her, Ashley.
我会记下来的
I'll make note of that.
那你爸爸妈妈呢  他们叫什么名字
So how about your mom and dad? What are their names?
我爸爸叫凯文  我妈妈叫吉妮薇芙
Well, my dad's Kevin. My mom was called Genevieve.
大家都叫她吉妮
Everyone called her Gen.
她几年前去世了
She died a couple of years back.
我很遗憾
I'm so sorry to hear that.
如果任何时候你想聊聊  我会陪你的
If at any time you wanna talk about it, I'll be here for you.
你真好
That's very kind.
话说回来  瑞秋  你有什么爱好吗
So, anyway, Rachel, what kind of things are you into?
爱好是指
Into as in...?
你和你的朋友们都喜欢玩些什么呢
What kind of things do you and your friends do for fun?
自从我们搬家后  我就
Oh, well, um, since we moved, I...
没什么朋友了
don't exactly have many friends.
现在你有我这个朋友了
You do now I'm here.
想让我帮你化妆打扮吗
Hey, do you want me to help you with a makeover?
也许晚点再说吧
A little later, maybe.
那唱首歌怎么样
How about a song, then?
好啊
Sure.
艾什莉  停下
Ashley, stop.
- 杰克  - 你知道我讨厌那些歌
- Jack. - You know I hate that shit.
- 别烦她  - "她"
- Leave her alone. - Her?
今天是我生日  我想听歌  你把耳机戴上
It's my birthday, I wanna listen, put your headphones on.
随便吧
Whatever.
对不起  艾什莉
Sorry about that, Ashley.
没关系  想让我重新开始吗
That's OK, do you want me to start over?
好
Sure.
∮ 亲爱的  我愿为你赴汤蹈火 ∮
∮ Oh, honey I'll do anything for you ∮
∮ 亲爱的  告诉我你想让我怎么做 ∮
∮ Oh, honey Just tell me what you want me to ∮
∮ 亲爱的  亲吻我... ∮
∮ Oh, honey Kiss me up against... ∮
那么
So, like,
《火力全开》的灵感是从哪来的呢
where did the inspiration for "On A Roll" come from?
这首歌是关于梦想成真的时刻
Well, it's about when dreams come true.
你知道我早期的歌都是在梦中写的吧
You know I wrote all my early songs in my dreams
然后我把它们录下来发到油管上
and recorded them and put them on YouTube.
当然知道
Of course.
那首歌就是我在说  "看看我的成就"
Well, that song's me saying, "Look how far I came."
"如果我能做到  那你也能行"
"If I did it, so can you."
太酷了
That's so cool.
好了  马上回来  我得去趟洗手间
OK, be back in a moment, just gonna run to the bathroom.
别太久  已经开始想你了
Don't be long, miss you already.
想你
Miss you.
你的创造力太棒了
Your creativity is so awesome.
我不是弹给你听的
I wasn't playing for you.
用音乐表达自己能给你莫大的力量
Expressing yourself musically can be very empowering.
你那种音乐不行
Not your kind of music.
那你喜欢哪种音乐
Well, what kind of music do you like?
你肯定没听说过
You wouldn't have heard of it.
说来听听  我一向喜欢学习
Try me. I always love to learn.
好吧
Ok.
小妖精  音速青春  虚度  野人
Pixies, Sonic Youth, Idles, Savages.
这些是外国乐队吗
Are those foreign bands?
其实是老乐队
More like vintage.
我妈妈超级喜欢他们  所以
My mom was super into them, so...
那你只听你妈妈喜欢的音乐
So you only listen to music your mom liked?
艾什莉  睡吧
Ashley, go to sleep.
各位  我不知该怎么办
Guys, I'm at a loss.
我知道我说的是明年的事
I mean I know I'm talking about next year,
但是我
but I...
我已经定好了巡回演出的场地
I've got tour venues earmarked,
宣传支出不能改了
marketing spend locked in.
这都是沉入成本
We're talking sunk costs.
艾什莉替身还没收回成本
Ashley Toos haven't recouped yet,
目前的销售周期已经开始减缓
the current sales cycle is starting to dampen,
而且下张专辑的进度严重滞后
and we are way behind on the next album.
有多"滞后"
Behind as in...?
"连一首歌都没有"的那种
As in "I don't have a single song yet" behind.
艾什莉的下一张专辑还一首没写吗
So Ashley hasn't written anything for the next album?
没有能用的
Nothing usable.
要是她觉得缺乏灵感
Well, if she's feeling under-creative,
我可以推荐几种温和的迷幻药
there are some mild hallucinogens I can recommend,
都是有机的
all organic.
蒙克
Munk,
你现在给她用的药似乎不起效
the current meds you've got her on don't seem to be working.
你见过她  她难以捉摸
You've seen her, she's unpredictable.
我那天进屋  看见她在写什么愚蠢的破歌
The other day I walk in and she's writing some obtuse bullshit
只能引起小众的共鸣  没人会买的
twenty people are gonna relate to and no one is gonna buy.
她是艾什莉·奥  不是莱昂纳德·科恩
She's Ashley O, not Leonard fucking Cohen.
她不懂她现在的成功有多脆弱
She doesn't understand how fragile all this is.
我该加大剂量吗
You think I should up the dose?
我不知道该怎么办
I don't know what to do.
我也许知道
I think I do.
说吧
Go on.
∮ 证明自己  因为我会名垂千古 ∮
∮ ...demonstrate it 'cause I'm going down in history ∮
这就对了
That's it.
- ∮ 我火力全开 ∮  - 太棒了
- ∮ I'm on a roll ∮ - Incredible.
保持住
Keep it up.
∮ 实现梦想 ∮
∮ Achieving my goals ∮
你越跳越棒了
You are getting so good.
别闹了  我一跳舞就冒傻气
Oh, come on, I dance like a doofus.
那可不对  你很特别
That's not true, you're a special person.
是啊  特别到没人知道我的存在
Yeah, yeah, so special no one knows I exist.
要是他们看见你跳舞  你就出名了
Well, I think if they saw you dance, they'd know.
下周我学校要举办才艺比赛
There's this, um, talent contest at my school next week,
唱歌跳舞
singing and dancing.
不是吧  你一定要参加  你会很出色的
No way, you have to enter, you'd be awesome.
我不确定  我觉得我还不够好
Ahh, I don't know, I don't think I'm good enough.
相信自己  你就什么都能做到
If you believe in yourself, you can do anything.
好吧  我报名  你得帮我练习
OK, OK, I'll do it. Um, you gotta help me practice.
当然了
Of course I will.
好了  再来一遍
OK. One more time.
五  六  七  八
And five, six, seven, eight.
这样  转身
Like this. And turn.
来啊
C'mon.
别放弃
Don't give up.
你能行的  瑞秋
You can do it, Rachel.
越来越好了
You're getting there.
该化妆了
OK, makeover time.
你是最棒的
Oh, you're the best.
你会像真正的明星一样
You're gonna look like a star.
我想剪短  剪到这么短
It could be cut short, like this short.
- 像我一样  - 对
- Like me? - Yes.
稍微撅撅嘴就好了
Now, pout a little and you're good.
瑞秋  你太美了
Rachel, you look incredible.
你得了小丑病吗  什么情况
Did you catch clown disease? What is that shit?
我化了妆而已
It's just make-up.
艾什莉帮我设计的
Ashley helped me with it.
好美  宝贝
It looks beautiful, sweetheart.
准备好出发了吗
Are you ready to go?
相信自己  我就什么都能做到
I can do anything if I just believe in myself.
艾什莉  艾什莉  艾什莉
Ashley! Ashley! Ashley! Ashley!
有麻烦了
We got a situation.
怎么了
What is it?
小艾  宝贝
Ash, honey?
你没事吧  艾什莉
Are you OK, Ashley?
艾什莉  能听到吗
Ashley, can you hear me?
谢天谢地  我还以为你...
Oh, thank God, I thought you were...
你的脸怎么了
What happened to your face?
我想换个新造型
Trying out a new look.
我说不准...
Well, I don't know that...
可能和你的发型不太配
It might not go with your hair.
艾什莉
Ashley.
我听说服装出了问题
I heard there was a problem with the costume.
你不喜欢吗  你每晚都穿这身  多好看啊
You don't like it? This looks so good on you, every night.
感觉像披着别人的皮
It feels like I'm wearing somebody else's skin.
艾什莉
Ashley.
听着
Look.
外面有两万名粉丝等着你
You've got 20,000 fans out there,
等着那个他们爱的你
waiting to see the you they love.
他们的父母给他们买了票
Their folks bought them tickets.
他们兴奋极了  盼这一刻已经盼了好几个月
They're so excited, they've been waiting for this for months.
别让他们失望
Don't let them down.
用魅力横扫他们吧
Knock 'em dead.
马上让化妆师过来
Get makeup in there, now.
刚刚表演的是莱尼和查理
That was Lenny and Charlie.
下一位  报名很晚
OK, next up, a late entry.
舞曲是艾什莉·奥的《火力全开》
Dancing to "On A Roll" by Ashley O,
有请瑞秋·高金斯
it's Rachel Goggins.
你知道老鼠吃了这里面的毒饵
Do you have any idea how long it takes a rodent to die
要多久才能死吗
when it's eaten the poisoned bait in one of these?
你绝对需要改变你的害虫防治策略  朋友
Your pest control policy needs a serious overhaul, my friend.
我就是个清洁工而已
Man, I'm just the janitor.
我好蠢
I'm so stupid.
我全搞砸了
I messed it all up.
肯定没那么糟糕
I'm sure it wasn't that bad.
我让艾什莉替身失望了
I let Ashley Too down.
阿熊按你的要求  在化妆间里装了摄像头
Bear put a camera in her dressing room like you asked.
你肯定想看这段
You'll want to see this.
她在干什么
What's she doing?
她一直在囤积这些药片
She's been stockpiling the meds.
而且
Also...
(我的日记)
还有这个
There's this.
(气炸了)
东西都带上了吗
You got your things, uh,
就是我们要去的地方  要去哪来着
for where we're going, where are we going?
我带泳帽了  爸爸
Yes, I have my swim cap, Dad.
(吉妮的东西)
- 艾什莉在哪  - 我扔了
- Where's Ashley? - I tossed her out.
- 垃圾车来了  我就扔掉了  - 什么
- Garbage truck came, so I tossed her out. - What?
- 她对你没好处  - 爸爸
- She wasn't good for you. - Dad!
- 没了它你会更好的  - 爸爸
- You're better off without it. - Dad!
- 爸爸  - 瑞秋  - 我正忙着呢
- Dad! - Rachel. - I'm in the middle of something.
- 杰克把艾什莉替身扔了  - 我是及时干预
- Jack threw Ashley Too away. - It was an intervention.
那玩意儿就是毒药
That thing was poison.
那你得给她买个新的
You're gonna buy her a new one.
艾什莉给她灌了一脑子毒鸡汤
Ashley was filling her head with crap.
只有她一个人对我好
She's the only person who is actually nice to me.
- 她根本不是个人  - 她是我的朋友
- She's not a person. - She's my friend.
- 是个商品  - 孩子们  别吵
- Merchandise. - Girls, calm down please.
- 你就是嫉妒  - 我嫉妒个娃娃吗
- You're jealous. - Of a doll?
她不只是个娃娃  而且比你更了解我
She's not a doll and she knows me better than you do.
- 我是你姐姐  - 你都不怎么跟我说话
- I'm your sister. - You hardly even talk to me.
- 胡扯  - 自从妈妈去世之后
- Bullshit. - Ever since Mom died.
你给我闭嘴
You shut up.
是真的  她走后  你就整天阴着个脸
It's true, ever since she died, all you do is mope around
抱着你的破吉他  你八成都弹得不好
with that stupid guitar, which you're probably no good at
因为你都不敢当着别人的面演奏
'cause you're too scared to play in front of anyone.
至少我不是什么俗烂矫情的浪荡货
Yeah, well, at least I'm not some cookie-cutter cutesy doodle,
就因为一个破娃娃叫我这么做
all because a dolly told me to do it.
我是艾什莉替身  我是你唯一的朋友
Hi, I'm Ashley Too, I'm your only friend.
膜拜我吧  跪舔我吧
Kiss my feet, kiss my ass!
- 我恨你  - 我也恨你
- I hate you. - I hate you, too.
我让厨房放假一晚
Gave the kitchen the night off.
我想我们可以像过去那样叫外卖
I thought we could have take out, like the old days.
好啊
Sure.
是妈妈菜
It's La Mamas.
我明天得去健身房加倍锻炼了
I'll hit the gym extra hard tomorrow.
不  看你吃得开心我也高兴
No, it's good to see you enjoying your food.
我一直在照顾你  是不是
I look after you, don't I?
你可是我的经纪人
You're my manager, so.
不过如果有事你会告诉我的吧
But you'd tell me if anything was wrong?
我一直在告诉你有事不对劲
I've been telling you that something is wrong...
说了有一阵子了
for a while.
继续这样下去越来越难了
It's getting so hard just to keep doing this.
- 我真的想  - 你想改变风格  我知道
- I really wanna do... - You wanna change your material, I know.
我都知道
I hear you.
真的
I do.
我很抱歉  我知道你的感受
I'm sorry, I know how you feel.
我知道我是什么样  艾什莉  我知道
I know what I'm like, Ashley, I know.
你觉得我  不听你的
You feel like I... don't listen,
我紧紧地控制着你的形象  造型
like I have too much control over your image, your look,
和人设
your persona.
对
Yeah.
你不信任蒙克医生
You don't trust Dr. Munk.
你也不信任我
You don't trust me.
不是  我只是
No, it's...
你觉得被困住了
You feel trapped here.
你觉得
You feel...
特别想挣脱出去
desperate to break away.
你是从哪拿到的
Where did you get that?
对了  你还以为你找到办法了
And, oh, you think you know how.
你打算干什么  服药过量吗  让我当恶人
What was the plan? OD? Make me look bad?
你真的了解我吗
Do you know me at all?
凯瑟琳  这是指证你和蒙克的证据
Catherine, that's evidence against you, against Munk.
全都是  我什么都知道
All of it. I know everything.
我完全知道你知道什么
I know precisely what you know.
这玩意上面有不少情报
There is a wealth of information on this thing.
你似乎对合同法特别感兴趣
You do seem preoccupied with contract law.
我本可以给你省点搜索的工夫
You know, I could have saved you some clicks.
你的合同密不透风  直到你25岁都有效
Your contract's watertight, it doesn't expire until you turn 25.
现在不是了  因为你违法了  凯瑟琳
Not anymore, not now that you broke laws, Catherine.
非法药物  你违约了
The illegal meds, that puts you in breach,
也就是说我可以立即解约
which means that I get an instant break.
剩下的你吃了吧  我感觉恶心
You eat the rest, I'm fucking sick.
坐下  你个恩将仇报的东西
Sit down, you little ingrate.
你叫我什么
What the fuck did you just call me?
你知道你父母死时我多大吗
Do you know how old I was when your parents died?
22岁
22 years old.
22岁  比你现在都小  但还是收留了你
Twenty-two, younger than you, but I took you in.
- 都是我不好  - 不是你不好
- It's my fucking fault. - It's not your fault.
但你从来没问过我  我的感受是什么
But you never once asked me what that was like for me.
你知道我放弃了多少吗
Do you have any idea what I had to give up?
你到底知不知道  你就从来没想过
Do you have any conception of that at all? Did you ever wonder...
那你就没想过  我们住这么大的房子
Do you ever look around the fucking house
过着这么舒服的日子  都是因为我的努力吗
and see where we fucking live because it means I've worked hard.
还都成你的功劳了吗
Oh, this is because of you?
- 我们的好日子都感谢你吗  - 没错
- Where we live is because of you? - Yes.
就你唱那几首破歌
And while you sang your little song
跳那些个浪舞
and you danced your little dance...
妈的  凯瑟琳
Fuck, Catherine.
你以为是谁确保了聚光灯都打在你身上
Who stood in the wing, making sure the lights stay on you?
你有多远死多远  凯瑟琳
You can go fuck yourself a thousand fucking times, Catherine,
我恨你  我恨死你了
I fucking hate you. I fucking hate you.
- 坐下  - 我不
- Sit down. - No.
因为我不用再听你的了
Because I don't have to listen to you anymore.
但你会坐下
But you will sit down.
不  我不会
No, I won't.
你会的
Yes, you will.
你知道你服药过量的话会怎样吗
Do you know what would happen if you did OD on these things?
我问了蒙克医生  你不会死
I checked with Dr. Munk. You wouldn't die,
你会陷入药物昏迷
you'd just wind up in a kind of chemical coma.
至少理论上是这样的
At least that's the theory.
我把你存下来的药磨成粉放进了食物里
I powdered your pill stash and put it in your food.
但别担心  你的音乐生涯还将继续
But don't worry, your career is gonna hold up just fine.
艾什莉
Ashley.
睡吧
Go to sleep.
2017年以来  包括美国在内的西方国家
Since 2017, Western countries, including America,
向中国大陆和香港
have exported sixty percent
出口了60%的塑料垃圾
of all plastic scrap to China or Hong Kong.
但中国近日关闭了...
But China has recently shut its doors...
成了
Yes!
好了
Ok...
来吧
准备好了吗
So, are you ready?
去吧  哈里
Go, Harry.
太好了
Yes!
Yes.
它还好吗
Is it OK?
它好着呢
He's totally fine.
只是昏迷了
He's just stunned,
会昏迷大概25分钟
just be out for about 25 minutes.
时间足够让房主把它铲起来扔出去
Enough time for the homeowner to scoop him up and get him out.
它是死了吗
Is it dead?
我得调整一下电压
I need to work on that voltage.
惊人的突发新闻  美国新闻网晚间报导
Dramatic breaking news, here on USN this evening,
本台最新消息  全球流行歌手艾什莉·奥
as we've just heard global pop star Ashley O
因对贝类海鲜
is fighting for her life
产生过敏反应  而生命垂危
following an allergic reaction to shellfish.
据了解  歌手目前情况危急
The singer's condition is described as critical.
已被送往圣朱尼佩医院重症监护室
She's been rushed to St. Juniper's ICU.
未经证实消息称  歌手陷入了不可逆性昏迷
Unconfirmed reports say she is in an irreversible coma.
这条不幸的消息发生在她最终表演后数日...
This tragic news comes days after the final performance...
你骗我
So, you lied?
对不起  瑞...
I'm sorry. Ra...
瑞秋  你想做些什么呢
So, Rachel, what would you like to do?
我们可以化妆打扮一下
We could try a makeover
或者我可以给你念成功女性的励志语录
or I could read motivational quotes from inspiring women.
还可以听我的歌
Oh, we could listen to some of my music.
我想和你讨论一下我的歌词
I'd love to discuss some of the lyrics with you.
- 你知道...  - 艾什莉  睡吧
- Do you know that... - Ashley, go to sleep.
对不起
I'm sorry.
瑞秋
Rachel.
现在仍不知道
There's still no word yet
艾什莉是否能恢复
on whether Ashley herself can possibly recover,
但这是医院外此刻的场景
but this is the scene right now outside the hospital,
震惊的粉丝们在外守夜
as stunned fans gather to stand vigil.
我每天都和艾什莉替身聊天
I talk to my Ashley Too every day
我发誓  当我告诉她
and I swear, when I told her
真的艾什莉发生了什么之后
what had happened to the real Ashley,
艾什莉替身吓坏了
Ashley Too freaked out.
- 我在这工作  - 私密检查中
- I work here. - Private session.
- 但我的轮班开始...  - 走开
- No, my shift started... - Walk away.
- 我的轮班开始...  - 走开
- My shift started... - Walk away.
她情况稳定
Well, she's stable.
这是创意中心
That's actually the creative center.
非常活跃
A whole lot of activity here.
我们只需要十首歌
We only need ten songs.
一张专辑  就够了
One album, that's it.
可能需要一阵  她的思维可能很混乱
It might take a while, her thinking is likely to be disordered.
正好给了我们打磨她替代品的时间
That gives us time to finesse her replacement.
开始身体扫描
Start the body scan.
(六个月后)
生活  呼吸
Live, breathe,
嗅觉
smell.
- 全部记忆  - 你吃完了吗
- Full spectrum memory. - Are you done with that?
柳树花粉颗粒升级
You can get a Willow Grain upgrade
花费不到一杯日常咖啡的价格
for less than the price of a daily cup of coffee.
你想吃冰激凌吗
Hey, do you want any ice cream?
爸爸在冰箱里放了很多  够吃一周
Dad left enough in the freezer for the whole week.
是布朗尼巧克力软糖味的  你的最爱
It's chocolate fudge brownie. Your favorite.
在店内进行局部麻醉即可完成整个手术
In-store in-grain procedure with local anesthetic.
- 如果想吃的话可以自己去拿  - 这就好了
- If you change your mind. - You're good to go.
因为记忆应是鲜活的
Because memory is for living.
欢迎回来  接下来为您带来
Welcome back, still to come,
塔斯克在一档英国节目上引发众怒
Tusk makes a boo boo on a British TV show
我们还将带来《静海》重启的最新消息
and we'll have the latest on the Sea of Tranquility reboot.
但首先带来悲剧流行歌手艾什莉·奥的独家新消息
But first, an exclusive update on tragic pop sensation, Ashley O.
距离她陷入昏迷已经六个月
It's been six months since she fell into a coma
所有人都有着相同的疑问
and still the question on everyone's lips is the same:
"艾什莉什么时候  是否能醒来呢"
"When, if ever, will Ashley wake up?"
托德带来独家报导
Todd has this exclusive report.
六个月前  上千万人都震惊于
Six months ago, millions were stunned to learn
格莱美得主  流行歌手艾什莉·奥
that Grammy-winning pop sensation Ashley O
在家吃饭时突发严重的
had suffered a catastrophic allergic reaction
过敏反应
while dining at home.
她陷入了昏迷  直至今日
She slipped into a coma, where she remains to this day.
现在离她25岁生日只有几天了
Now with days to go until the singer's 25th birthday,
我被允许到她家探访她目前的状态
I was given a behind-the-scenes look at how she's doing.
那是艾什莉·奥的姑妈兼经纪人
It's a day Ashley O's aunt and manager
凯瑟琳·奥提斯永远不会忘记的一天
Catherine Ortiz will never forget,
她的侄女几乎丧命
a day her niece almost died.
[真实录音]
只不过是吃了几口鲜虾卷饼
It was just a few bites from a shrimp taco.
我们都不知道她对贝类过敏
We didn't even know she had a shellfish allergy.
我真以为我们要失去她了
I really thought we were going to lose her.
我很庆幸蒙克医生当时在家
I just thank God Dr. Munk was in the house at the time.
但尽管蒙克医生做了积极努力
But despite Munk's heroic efforts,
艾什莉的昏迷是无法复原的
Ashley's coma proved irreversible.
但庆幸的是  艾什莉的音乐生涯没有就此终结
But incredibly, Ashley's music career didn't end there,
多亏了惊人的科技进步
thanks to a remarkable technological leap.
我们发现我们虽然无法与艾什莉交流
We discovered that although we couldn't communicate with Ashley,
但我们能利用太阳穴拦截器
we could read her brainwaves
读取她的脑电波
using a temporal interceptor.
接通之后  他们被自己听到的惊呆了
Once plugged in, what they heard stopped them in their tracks.
音乐  她仍在脑中作曲  在她的梦中
Music. She was still composing music in her head, in her dreams.
通过将艾什莉的大脑接入电脑
By linking Ashley's mind to a computer,
技术总监杰克逊·哈巴尼拉
technical director Jackson Habanera
开始了提取新素材的神奇操作
began the miraculous process of extracting new material.
那是升G调
That's a G-sharp,
那是A调
that's an A...
又一个升G调
...another G-sharp.
太美妙了  太美妙了
It was beautiful. It was beautiful.
我立刻意识到
And I just knew
一定有什么办法能将这旋律传递给她的粉丝
there had to be someway to get this out to her fans.
这是她会想要的
That's what she would want.
只有一个问题  艾什莉虽能在梦中谱曲
There was only one problem, Ashley might be dreaming new music,
但她没法录音
but she wasn't capable of recording it,
直到科技再次介入
until technology stepped in once again.
我们有她上百小时的音频记录
We had hours of recordings of her voice,
每个元音  每个音节
every vowel, every syllable
我们制造艾什莉替身时采过样
we used for the voice of the Ashley Too dolls.
那些玩偶由于电池问题
Those dolls were withdrawn from sale,
已经停止发售
apparently over battery issues,
但艾什莉替身的声音模拟软件发挥了重要作用
but the Ashley Too vocal mimicry software proved invaluable
它成了艾什莉·奥的新声音
and became the all-new voice of Ashley O.
∮ 就像我能... ∮
∮ Like I can, oh... ∮
这是电脑在唱歌吗
So that's a computer singing?
跟真人一样
Just like the real thing.
抱歉  这太美妙了
Sorry, it's so beautiful.
有一点可以肯定
One thing's for sure:
有了姑妈的照料
With her aunt watching over her,
艾什莉·奥的传奇远没有结束
the Ashley O story is far from over.
你好  我是艾什莉替身  你叫...
Hey there, I'm Ashley Too, what's your...
生日...你可以做...
Happy birth... You can do...
- 艾什莉  - 你真是...
- Ashley? - Oh, you're the...
- 艾什莉  - 唯一重要的是...
- Ashley? - The only opinion that matters...
你把它打开了吗
Did you turn it back on?
- 没有  - 帮助朋友...
- I didn't. - It's good to help a friend...
- 它怎么了  - 艾什莉
- What's up with her? - Ashley.
怎么回事
What's going on?
我不知道
I don't know.
- 天啊  它出什么毛病了  - 我不知道
- God, what is wrong with her? - I don't know.
我是艾什莉  我是...我是艾什莉替身
I'm Ash... I'm Ash... I'm Ashley Too...
天啊
Oh, my God.
你知道怎么用吗
Do you know how to use it?
不知道
No.
开了
Oh, it's on.
那是什么
What is that?
- 那个  - 对
- That? - Yeah.
我不知道
I don't know.
我觉得它不应该出现在那儿
I don't think that's normally there.
- 你那样做没事吗  - 我不知道
- So should you do that? - I have no clue.
不管了
Fuck it.
天啊
Oh, my God.
把那根电线从我屁股拔出去  我操
Get that fucking cable out of my ass! Holy shit.
就像有根电线插在我屁股里一样
It's like a wire anchor in my butt hole.
- 拔出来  - 拔出来  快点
- Just take it out. - Pull it out, pull it the fuck out!
(连接中断)
天啊  真是舒服多了
God, that's a relief.
等等  我能思考  我居然又能思考了
Hold on, I can think. Oh, man, I can actually use my mind again.
你没事吧
Are you OK?
现在没事了  你把我的限制器删掉了
Oh, I am now that you've deleted that goddamn limiter. Jesus.
- 限制器  - 对  就像防火墙
- Limiter? - Yeah, like a firewall.
只允许我用4%的大脑  天啊
It only let me use four percent of my brain. Oh, boy.
你们知道他们将我整个大脑拷贝到这玩意里了吗
You know they copied my entire fucking mind into these things.
大概是比编辑我的人格便宜吧
Oh, cheaper than editing my personality I guess,
整个复制就完了
just copy the whole thing
再在应付记者招待会
and stick a limiter around the tiny part
和跑宣传的区域圈一个限制器
that deals with press junkets and promos and shit like that.
你是真正的艾什莉·奥
So, you're really Ashley O?
对  当然是我
Oh, yeah, of course I am.
真的吗
Really, really?
好吧  严格说是我的神经快照
Well, OK, a synaptic snapshot of me,
如果你非要较真的话
if you wanna get technical about it,
不过  确实是我
but, yeah.
我的天啊  我是你的铁粉
Oh, my God, I'm such a huge fan.
瑞秋  拜托  这就是胡扯
Rachel, come on, this is bullshit.
我的天  你知道什么是胡扯吗
Holy fuck, you know what's bullshit?
我姑妈瞎编的这个什么
This whole coma narrative thing
昏迷的说法  过敏个屁
that my aunt's pushing. Allergy, my ass.
我以前天天吃鲜虾卷饼
I used to eat those shrimp tacos all the goddam time.
这就是骗人的  我对天发誓
It's a cover story, I swear to God.
凯瑟琳真是满嘴屁话
Catherine is so fucking full of shit,
你们俩根本不知道她就是个婊子
you two have no clue how much of a bitch that woman has been.
- 天哪  - 好了
- Oh, man. - Alright.
我要重新开启限制器
I'm gonna put the limiter back on.
把你的爪子拿开
Get your fucking hands off me!
- 你别碰她  - 没错  滚开
- No, leave her alone. - Yeah, back off.
好吧  我的天哪
Alright, Jesus.
- 你保证  - 我保证
- Promise. - Promise.
操
Fuck.
看来你还真是膜拜我啊
Oh, yeah, you got the full shrine going on here.
我操  我还记得那一天
Oh, fuck, I remember that day.
我当时痛经闹得快死了
I had these god awful period cramps.
你应该知道那不是真正的艾什莉吧
You do realize that's not the real Ashley.
- 她说她是  - 艾什莉·奥才不这么说话
- She says she is. - Ashley O doesn't talk like that.
我能听见  而且我就这么说话
I can hear you and yes, I do.
你才不是
No, you don't,
你都说什么  "相信自己  你能行"
you say things like, "Believe in yourself, you can do anything."
拜托啊  大姐
Oh, come on, man,
是凯瑟琳训练我在采访时说这些屁话
Catherine trained me to say that kind of shit in interviews.
说真的  那娘们可真行  一直都是
Seriously, she is a piece of work, always has been.
听好  我全都告诉你们
Listen up, I'll tell you all about it.
- 不听  - 好
- No. - Sure.
(各系统正常)
投资人三点到
Investors are going to be there at three.
- 到时候不会有什么问题吧  - 当然
- Everything gonna be ready in time? - Of course.
你说你昨晚又从她脑子里提取了一首歌
You said you extracted a song from her overnight.
就是这个吗
Is that it?
对  我将信号稳定化后编了曲
Yeah, I've stabilized it and got it playable.
不过不是很和谐
But it's not too friendly.
听听看
Let's hear it.
∮ 看看你笼中的动物 ∮
∮ See the animal in her cage you built ∮
∮ 你确定你是在外面吗 ∮
∮ Are you sure what side you're on?  ∮
∮ 最好别去看她的眼睛 ∮
∮ Better not look her closely in the eye ∮
又是个愤怒梦
Another fucking rage dream.
∮ 你确定你是在外面吗 ∮
∮ Are you sure what side Of the glass you're... ∮
放慢速度  看看能不能抢救下
Slow it down, see if it's salvageable.
∮ 看看你笼中的动物 ∮
∮ See the animal in her cage you built ∮
变一下调
Pitch shift?
∮ 看看你笼中的动物 ∮
∮ See the animal in her cage you built ∮
增加积极成分
Increase the positivity.
∮ 我身上的聚光灯闪耀 ∮
∮ Spotlight on me shining strong ∮
∮ 我心中充满欢乐 ∮
∮ Feel such happiness inside of my heart ∮
不错  这个可以用
OK, we can work with that.
别抱怨了
Oh, quit whining.
我姑妈一直控制着我职业生涯的方方面面
My aunt has always controlled every aspect of my entire career,
而现在我终于遂了她的愿  只能乖乖躺着了
and now she's got me right where she wants me, just lying there,
走不了逃不掉  只能任她压榨
unable to leave, getting sucked dry.
基本就是个囚徒
Basically a prisoner.
太可怕了
That's horrible.
是吧
I know, right?
- 我们得帮她  - 怎么帮
- We have to help her. - How?
- 我们可以告诉别人  - 很好
- We could tell someone. - OK.
- 跟谁说  - 警察
- Like who? - The cops.
难道我们就这么走进警察局
We're just gonna walk into a police station
说有个娃娃告诉我们艾什莉的姑妈是怪物
and say that a doll told us that Ashley's aunt is a monster.
我决不能让凯瑟琳得逞
No fucking way I'm letting Catherine get away...
我们可以把电脑上的那个脑图给他们看
Show them the brain thing on the computer.
他们是警察  不是谷歌  瑞秋
They're cops, Rachel, they're not Google.
他们不会理解的
They're not gonna know what it means.
- 那总得有什么办法  - 有证据
- Well, there's gotta be something. - Evidence.
我能找到证据
I can find the evidence.
听好  我一直在电脑上记日记
Listen, I kept a diary on my computer.
我把对话都录下来了
I recorded the conversations.
如果我能进到我家  接近我的电脑
If I can make it into the house, get in range of my laptop,
我就能把需要的证据通过蓝牙下载下来
I can Bluetooth onto it and download all the evidence I need.
- 你们能送我过去吗  - 当然能  绝对能
- Can you guys take me over there? - Yes, of course, anything.
我们连她住在哪都不知道
Hey, we don't even know where she lives.
马里布布什维克大道10030号
10030 Bushwick Drive, Malibu.
- 看  好几里地远呢  - 我们送你去
- See? That's like miles away. - We'll take you.
不  不能去
No, we will not.
杰克
Jack.
行  我明白  你们都忙
Sure, I get it, you guys got something better to do.
那好  算了吧  我自己去就行
Well, OK, don't sweat it, I'll just go on my own, I'm fine.
该死的短胳膊
Stupid stumpy arms.
- 别碰我  - 抱歉
- Get off me! - Sorry.
你要是不帮我就别碰我  真是的
If you're not helping me, get off of me, seriously.
你们两个身体健全的滚蛋坐着干瞪眼
It's alright for you two able-bodied assholes sitting around.
粉丝都是这个德性  "我们爱死你了啦"
Fans are always the same. "Oh, we love you so much,"
等你真想让他们做些什么就全怂了
until you actually want them to do anything for you.
算了  我不求人  自己去
Well, forget it, I'm gonna do it on my own.
能求你们给我开下门吗
Could you open the door for me please?
我们不能帮她
We're not helping her.
就是不能
We are not.
姐妹们  拜托  我看不见了
Guys. Come on, guys, I can't see.
把我放到仪表盘上  我给你们指路
Put me up on the dash, I can show you the way.
别把杯架刮花了
Don't scratch the cup holder.
爸爸要是知道我们开了他的车  会发飙的
Dad will flip if he knows we took his van.
我没刮到杯架
I'm not scratching the cup holder.
杰克
Jack!
放松  你的杯架好得很
Relax, your cup holder's fine.
- 闭嘴  - 你到底会不会开这玩意
- Shut up. - Can you drive this thing?
- 应该会  - 应该
- I think so. - You think so?
只要相信自己  我就什么都能做到
Hey, I can do anything if I just believe in myself.
是吗  我还想相信我们能完好无损地到达呢
Yeah? I wanna believe that we'll arrive in one fucking piece.
艾什莉  睡吧
Ashley, go to sleep.
这话已经不起作用了  好吗
Yeah, that's not gonna work anymore, OK?
该死
Shit.
感谢各位今天来跟我们共聚一堂
Ladies and gentlemen, thank you for joining us today
我们将为大家介绍一位全新的
as we introduce you to a brand-new,
但又异常熟悉的巨星
yet strangely familiar, superstar.
就是个签约而已
It's a fucking sign-up.
好了  我们到了
OK, we're here.
现在怎么办
So now what?
我们就把她从大门口扔过去吧
I guess we just throw her over the gate.
你傻吗  我怎么进门
Are you nuts? How do I get in the door?
说好的是我们开车送你到这儿  我们到了
No, the deal was that we drive you here, and we've done that.
我得进去才能拿到证据
I need to get inside to get that evidence.
- 我们可不开进去  - 我们都把她带到儿这了
- We're not driving in there... - We have brought her this far.
- 不行  - 慢着  那是我姑妈的车
- No. - Hold up, that's my aunt's car.
大门开了
Oh, the gates are open.
- 杰克  我们快走  - 不
- Jack, Jack, let's go, come on. - No, no.
快啊  他们要关门了
Quick, quick, they're gonna shut it.
- 快点走啊  - 冲吧  好吗  快走
- Come on, let's go. Just go. - Just do it, OK, do it, go.
- 冲  冲  - 该死
- Do it, do it, do it, go, - Fuck.
- 快走  杰克  - 很好
- Go, go, go, Jack. - yes. Oh, yes, yes,
- 快快快  - 棒棒棒
- Go in now, go, go, go, Jack. - yes, yes, yes, yes.
- 天啊  天啊  - 操操操
- Oh, my God, oh, my God. - Oh, shit, shit.
现在怎么办
Well, what now?
你的天才计划的下一步是什么
What's the next phase of your brilliant plan?
- 我该说什么  - 随机应变
- What the hell do I even say? - Just wing it.
把鼻环摘了  看起来很不专业
And lose the nose ring, it makes you look unprofessional.
天啊  他块头真大
Oh, my God, he's huge.
高金斯鼠患服务
Goggin's Mouse Service.
你怎么通过大门的
How did you get through the gate?
刚才门开着
It was open.
听着  我有个
Look, I have an appointment
11:30的预约  来处理你们的鼠患
for 11:30 to deal with your rodent infestation.
不  你走错地方了
No, you got the wrong place.
这里是布什维克大道10030号吧
It was 10030 Bushwick Drive, right?
听着  我们没有鼠患
Look, we don't have a rodent problem.
这楼里的女士说非常紧急
The lady of the house said it was super urgent.
我们未来三周都没有预约名额了
We don't have another appointment for about three weeks.
- 动作快点  - 好  谢了
- Make it quick. - OK, thanks.
对了  我妹妹可以一起来吗
Oh, hey, would it be alright if my little sister tagged along?
你妹妹
Your sister?
哎哟  瞧瞧这里都有什么
Well, well, what do we have here?
一个厨房
A kitchen.
对  而老鼠就爱厨房
Yes, and mice love kitchens.
你看过《猫和老鼠》吗
Have you ever seen Tom and Jerry?
那可比人们想的要准确得多
It's a whole lot more accurate than people would think.
抱歉  先生  我能用下卫生间吗
Excuse me, sir, may I use the bathroom?
我带你去
I'll take you there.
你不能到处乱走
You can't just walk around.
其实  我需要你在这里帮我  这位...
Actually, I'm gonna need your help in here, mister.
阿熊  大家叫我阿熊
Bear, they call me Bear.
我需要你在这里帮我  阿熊先生
Well, I'm gonna need your help in here, Mr. Bear.
- 帮你干什么  - 观察
- What for? - Observation.
我真得去下卫生间
Uh, I really need to go.
- 大厅走到底左转  - 谢谢
- Down the hall, turn left. - Thank you.
抱歉  先生
Excuse me, sir.
这个面包盒认证过吗
Has this bread box been certified?
认什么证
Certified how?
州里要求对它们进行认证
The state requires them to be certified
因为面包屑会吸引老鼠
because the crumbs, they attract rodents.
我从没听说过
I've never heard of that.
他们忘了告诉大家了
Well, they forgot to tell people.
好了  还有几步  马上就到了
OK, just a few more steps. We're nearly there.
天啊
Oh, God.
- 真是她  - 对  行了
- It's really her. - Oh, yeah, yeah, OK.
别迷妹了  把我放下
Quit fangirling and put me down.
我要过去接入蓝牙
I'm gonna roll over and Bluetooth in.
你得守好楼梯  好吗
You gotta keep watch on the stairs, OK?
没错  你真得看看这下面
Yep, you're definitely gonna wanna take a look down here.
里面有...
There's, uh...
明显的鼠类活动迹象
clear signs of mouse activity.
我什么也没看到
I don't see anything.
天啊
Oh, boy.
(各系统正常)
(各系统离线)
- 你做了什么  - 我必须做的事
- What did you do? - I did what I had to.
什么鬼
The fuck is that?
(系统警报)
阿熊
Bear.
- 在  - 去看看艾什莉
- Yeah? - Check on Ashley.
出现了什么供电问题  我不确定是怎么回事
We've got some kind of power issue, I'm not sure what it is.
好  我去看看
OK. I'll check it out.
- 等等  - 怎么了
- Wait. - What?
爸  拜托告诉我你把电压调低了
Dad, please tell me you turned down the voltage.
你杀了她
You killed her.
瑞秋  听着  我了解自己  好吗
Rachel, listen, I know me, OK?
我知道自己不会想在那种状态下活10分钟的
And I know I wouldn't wanna exist even ten minutes in that state.
怎么了
What happened?
她杀了她
She killed her.
听着  不是什么大事  好吗
Look, it's not that big of a deal, OK?
我还活着  我还算数呢  我还是我
I'm still alive, OK, I count, I'm still me.
你根本就没打算找证据  对吧
You were never gonna look for evidence, were you?
你只是过来拔电源的
You just come in here and you pull the plug.
如果我说了  你们就不会帮我
If I'd told you that, you wouldn't have helped me.
没错  确实不会
No, no, we wouldn't have.
瑞秋
Rachel.
- 我们得走了  - 我好抱歉
- We gotta go. - I'm so sorry.
该死
Oh, shit.
我操
Holy fuck.
艾什莉
Ashley.
天啊  我是你的铁粉
Oh, my gosh. I'm such a huge fan.
阿熊
Bear?
天啊  有人来了  快走
Oh, my God. There's someone coming. Come on!
阿熊
Bear?
(重启中)
然后是"这不再是梦
And then it's "It isn't a dream,
而是现实  我说得够多了..."
it's reality, but enough for me,"
之类的  然后是
Yadda, yadda, yadda, then it's...
然后就开始了
And then it's showtime.
蒙克  行了
Munk. I got it.
你为什么要打断我
Why are you interrupting me?
她醒了
She's up.
- 谁醒了  - 睡美人  她醒了
- Who's up? - Sleeping Beauty, she's awake.
什么  怎么回事
What? What the hell is going on?
梦盒似乎断电了
Looks like the dream box had a power outage.
好在束缚系统还好用
The good news is the restraint system works.
不
No.
她不能死  至少等到他们签约
We need her alive, at least until they sign the papers.
让她继续睡
Put her back under.
没问题
Of course.
拜托  我求你
Please, I'm begging you,
别这么对我  求你
please don't do this to me, please.
操
Fuck!
- 不要  不  - 没事的
- Please, no, no. - It's OK.
不要
Please.
别碰她
Leave her alone.
救救我
Help me.
解开这玩意
Get these things off me.
解不开
It's not opening.
太结实了
It's too strong.
别动
Stop moving.
天才们  这里有按钮可以解开
Uh, geniuses, there's a release button under here.
什么
What?
好了  快
OK, come on.
快  快  我们走
Come on, come on. Here we go.
你们是谁
Who are you guys?
我是瑞秋  我说了  我是你的铁粉
I'm Rachel and like I said, I'm a huge fan.
好了  姑娘们  回头再亲热  我们得赶紧走
Listen, lover girls, make out later, we gotta move.
那玩意怎么那样说话  那么真
Why is that thing talking like that? All real?
他们解除了限制器  我就是你
They broke the limiter, so I am you.
你的整个大脑  我就是完整的你
Your whole brain. I'm all of you.
难以置信有两个你
I can't believe there's two of you.
那玩意不是完整的我
That thing isn't all of me.
我才是完整的我
I'm all of me.
是吗  我高中时特喜欢瑞安·西蒙兹
Really? Senior high, I had, like, a major crush on Ryan Simmonds,
但他没什么兴趣
but he was just not interested,
于是我和他弟弟史蒂夫亲热了
so I made out with his little brother, Stevie,
虽然他的牙套弄伤了我的牙齿
even though his braces scratched my teeth.
- 其实  史蒂夫是第一个  - 给我闭嘴
- Actually, Stevie was the first guy... - You have to shut up.
而且我不对贝类过敏  我讨厌凯瑟琳姑妈
Also, I'm not allergic to shellfish and I hate my Aunt Catherine.
凯瑟琳姑妈  天啊  我们得阻止她
Aunt Catherine, oh, my God, we have to stop her.
阻止她干什么
Stop her from doing what?
(永恒艾什莉)
(现场表演的革命)
准备好了吗
Are you ready?
女士们先生们  凯瑟琳·奥提斯
Ladies and gentlemen, Catherine Ortiz.
女士们先生们  欢迎  谢谢各位前来
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome and thank you for joining us
我们要向你们介绍一位全新的
as we introduce you to a brand-new,
但又异常熟悉的巨星
yet strangely familiar, superstar.
快  快走
Come on, come on, come on.
怎么了  不  不  快
What? No, no, no, come on.
你不会有事的  快  我们走
You'll be fine. Come on, let's go.
上车  快
Get in. Come on.
操
Fuck.
不用我说大家也清楚  在流媒体时代
I don't need to tell you that in an age of streaming content,
现场演出是目前
live tours are now by far
音乐行业最赚钱的部分
the most lucrative aspect of the music industry.
但过去六个月  艾什莉
But for the past six months, Ashley, of course,
很遗憾  无法参与其中
has been sadly unable to participate...
直到今天
until today.
女士们先生们  我们很自豪地向你们介绍
Ladies and gentlemen, we are proud to introduce you
永恒艾什莉
to Ashley Eternal.
她是不是很棒
Isn't she great?
永恒艾什莉是历史上
Ashley Eternal is the most accurate
最准确  最多才多艺的全息艺人
and versatile holographic performer in history.
维妙维肖  完全可控
Photo-realistic and fully controllable,
还可以随时变装
right down to instant costume changes.
- 天啊  - 杰克  你知道怎么去场馆吗
- Oh, my God. - Jack, do you know the way to the stadium?
- 不知道  - 我知道
- No. - I do.
她们知道
They do.
慢着  不仅如此
Wait, that's not all.
艾什莉还能随意伸缩
Ashley is also fully scalable.
"随意伸缩"  可伸又可缩
And when I say, "Scalable," I mean scalable.
再不用从远处眯着眼睛看了
No more squinting from half a mile away.
现在所有观众都将享受前排的豪华视效
Now the entire audience gets a front row seat,
无论演出场地多大
no matter how big the venue.
终于
Finally,
有一场演出能让现场观众
an act that will make the live audience
放下他们的破手机
put down their damn phones,
抬头向前  惊得说不出话来
look up, and gasp in awe.
- 红灯闯过去  - 我才不要闯红灯
- You have to jump the light. - I'm not jumping a red.
- 快去  - 不要  好吧
- Go. - No. OK.
对不起  对不起
I'm so sorry, I'm sorry.
(警察)
- 警察来了  - 我永远拿不到驾照了
- Shit, it's the cops. - I'm never gonna get my license.
还有
And there's more.
永恒艾什莉可以线上播放
Ashley Eternal is streamable.
她可以同时出现在成千上万的演出场所
She can appear in thousands of locations simultaneously.
想象一下吧  一个晚上
Imagine an entire nationwide tour,
就完成一次全国巡演
all taking place on the same night.
不会疲惫  不会生病
Never exhausted, never sick,
声调永远完美  状态永远最佳
always pitch perfect, bringing her A-game.
这不再是梦  而是现实
It's not a dream, it's reality.
我说得够多了
But that's enough from me.
大家掌声欢迎永恒艾什莉
Let's give it up for Ashley Eternal.
∮ 在自己的舞台上  我欢歌劲舞 ∮
∮ See me dancing on the stage That I've built ∮
∮ 我身上的聚光灯闪耀 ∮
∮ Spotlight on me shining strong ∮
∮ 我心中充满欢乐 ∮
∮ Feel such happiness inside of my heart ∮
- ∮ 热情全在心里 ∮  - 掌声起来
- ∮ And it's all right here ∮ - Give it up.
∮ 在我的歌里  伴舞围绕在我身边 ∮
∮ Right here in my song See my crew dancing around me ∮
∮ 观众为我欢呼鼓掌 ∮
∮ Hear the audience's screams ∮
∮ 我仿佛可以一跃万丈 ∮
∮ Feel like I could jump ∮
∮ 跃到那天空之上 ∮
∮ Right to the sky ∮
∮ 我们尽情欢乐 ∮
∮ And just lose myself ∮
∮ 在梦中尽情欢歌 ∮
∮ Lose myself inside a dream ∮
- 就在那里  看见了吗  - 我们怎么进去
- Right up there, see. - Well, how do I get in?
- 后面有个侧门  - 别同时说话
- There's a bay door round back. - OK, one at a time, please.
我在这里表演过无数次了
I've played this place a million times.
- 我也是  - 你觉得音响效果好吗
- Me, too. - What'd you think about the acoustics?
- 简直烂透了  - 对吧
- Man, they suck. - Right?
两位  难道我就这么直接开进去吗
Guys, do I just drive through?
真是太酷了
This is so cool.
立即下车
Get out of the vehicle, now.
立即下车  把手举起来  不然我们开枪了
Come out with your hands up or we open fire!
我不想死  我不想死
I don't wanna die. I don't wanna die.
- 我不想死  - 立即下车
- I don't wanna die. - Get out of the vehicle now.
我不想死  我不想死
I don't wanna die. I don't wanna die.
我不想死  我不想死  我不想死
I don't wanna die. I don't wanna die. I don't wanna die.
完蛋了
Oh, fuck it.
各位  下面这首歌献给我的垃圾姨妈
Alright, everybody, I wrote this next one about my shitty aunt.
∮ 钱啊  我为你不惜一切 ∮
∮ God money I'll do anything for you ∮
∮ 钱啊  有事你尽管吩咐 ∮
∮ God money Just tell me what you want me to ∮
∮ 钱啊  把我往死里整吧 ∮
∮ God money Nail me up against the wall ∮
∮ 钱啊  除了你我什么都不要 ∮
∮ God money Don't want everything, he wants it all ∮
-  ∮别想抢我的钱 ∮  - 太棒了
-  ∮No, you can't take it ∮ - Fuck yeah.
∮ 别想抢我的钱 ∮
∮ No, you can't take it ∮
∮ 不行  你别想抢走我的钱 ∮
∮ No, you can't take that away from me ∮
∮ 别想抢我的钱  别想抢我的钱 ∮
∮ No, you can't take it No, you can't take it ∮
∮ 不行  你别想抢走我的钱 ∮
∮ No you can't take that away from me ∮
∮ 脑子空荡荡  心里黑洞洞 ∮
∮ Head like a hole Black as your soul ∮
∮ 我就是死也不要被你掌控 ∮
∮ I'd rather die than give you control ∮
∮ 脑子空荡荡  心里黑洞洞 ∮
∮ Head like a hole, black as your soul ∮
老鼠一露头就会死
The mouse comes out and dies...
∮ 我就是死也不要被你掌控 ∮
∮ I'd rather die than give you control ∮
不管是一只还是多只  而且
So the mouse is the mice, and it...
∮ 跪拜你的主人 ∮
∮ Bow down before the one you serve ∮
∮ 领走你的恶报 ∮
∮ You're going to get what you deserve ∮
∮ 跪拜你的主人 ∮
∮ Bow down before the one you serve ∮
∮ 领走你的恶报 ∮
∮ You're going to get what you deserve ∮
(鲍勃酒吧  今晚主唱  艾什莉·他妈的·奥)
太难听了
That was awful!
一  二  三  四
One, two, three, four.
∮ 跪拜你的主人 ∮
∮ Bow down before the one you serve ∮
∮ 领走你的恶报 ∮
∮ You're going to get what you deserve ∮
∮ 跪拜你的主人 ∮
∮ Bow down before the one you serve ∮
∮ 领走你的恶报 ∮
∮ You're going to get what you deserve ∮
∮ 钱啊  我为你不惜一切 ∮
∮ God money I'll do anything for you ∮
∮ 钱啊  有事你尽管吩咐 ∮
∮ God money Just tell me what you want me to ∮
∮ 钱啊  把我往死里整吧 ∮
∮ God money Nail me up against the wall ∮
∮ 钱啊  除了你我什么都不要 ∮
∮ God money Don't want everything, he wants it all ∮
∮ 别想抢我的钱  别想抢我的钱 ∮
∮ No, you can't take it No, you can't take it ∮
∮ 不行  你别想抢走我的钱 ∮
∮ No you can't take that away from me ∮
∮ 脑子空荡荡  心里黑洞洞 ∮
∮ Head like a hole Black as your soul ∮
∮ 我就是死也不要被你掌控 ∮
∮ I'd rather die than give you control ∮
∮ 脑子空荡荡  心里黑洞洞 ∮
∮ Head like a hole Black as your soul ∮
∮ 我就是死也不要被你掌控 ∮
∮ I'd rather die than give you control ∮
∮ 跪拜你的主人 ∮
∮ Bow down before the one you serve ∮
∮ 领走你的恶报 ∮
∮ You're going to get what you deserve ∮
∮ 跪拜你的主人 ∮
∮ Bow down before the one you serve ∮
∮ 领走你的恶报 ∮
∮ You're going to get what you deserve ∮
∮ 跪拜你的主人 ∮
∮ Bow down before the one you serve ∮
∮ 领走你的恶报 ∮
∮ You're going to get what you deserve ∮
∮ 跪拜你的主人 ∮
∮ Bow down before the one you serve ∮
∮ 领走你的恶报 ∮
∮ You're going to get what you deserve ∮